BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VII: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.4402: Kollsman Instrument Corporation and International Association of Machinists, District 15, 1961-1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Code no.4110: Grayson Controls Division of Robertshaw Controls Company and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 805, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Code no.4409: Honeywell Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 1145, 1965-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Code no.4420: Westclox Division of General Time Corporation and United Mine Workers of America, Local 12573, District 50, 1966- 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Code no.4423: The United States Time Corporation (Timex Corporation) and Waterbury Watch Workers, Local 24369, 1959-1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Code no.4425: Clock and Timer Department of General Electric Company and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 205, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Code no.4427: Xerox Corporation and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Local 14A, Xerographic Division, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Code no.4600: Jewelry Manufacturers Association, Inc. and Amalgamated Jewelry, Diamond, and Watchcase Workers Union Local 1, 1969- 1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Code no.4607: National Association of Doll Manufacturers, Inc. and International Union of Dolls, Toys, Playthings, Novelties, and Allied Products of United States and Canada Local 223, Toy & Novelty Workers of America, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Code no.4608: A.G. Spalding & Bros., Inc. and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local Lodge 1851, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Code no.4609: Stuffed Toy Manufacturers Association, Inc. and International Union of Dolls, Toys, Playthings, Novelties, and Allied Products of United States and Canada Local 223, Toy & Novelty Workers of America, 1960-1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Code no.4610: Covered Button Association of New York and International Ladies Garment Workers Union Local 66, Bonnaz, Embroideries, Tucking, Pleating & Allied Crafts Union, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Code no.4614: Remco Industries, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 97, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Code no.4615: Mattel Inc. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, Locals 458 & 766, 1964- 1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Code no.4616: Louis Marx & Co. and Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union, United Toy Workers Union, Local 149, 1970- 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Code no.4617: Milton Bradley Co. and Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union Local 224, Milton Bradley Industrial Union, 1965- 1973 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Code no.590027: Johnson Service Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District 10, 1966- 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Code no.590027: Johnson Service Company and Steamfitters' Union Local 601, Service Division, 1966-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Code no.590027: Johnson Service Company and Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers and Allied Workers International Union Local 10, 1966- 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Code no.590027: Johnson Service Company and International Molders and Allied Workers' Union Local 125, 1966-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Code no.3373: Link-Belt Speeder Division of FMC Corporation and United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 299, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Code no.4087: Republic Aviation Corporation and Republic Lodge 1987 of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1960-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Code no.4088: ROHR Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Local 755, 1960-1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Code no.4089: ROHR Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 964, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Code no.4092: Thompson Ramo Wooldridge Inc. and Aircraft Workers Alliance, Inc., 1960-1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Code no.4093: United Aircraft Corporation Sikorsky Aircraft Division and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 877, Sikorsky Aircraft Unit, 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Code no.4093: United Aircraft Corporation Sikorsky Aircraft Division and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 1150, 1963-1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Code no.4095: Hamilton Standard Division of United Aircraft Corporation and International Association of Machinists Lodge 743, Building 3 Plant, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Code no.4097: Alabama Dry Dock and Shipbuilding Company and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 18, 1961-1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Code no.4098: American Ship Building Company and AFL-CIO, 1958-1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Code no.4099: Bath Iron Works Corporation and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 6, 1960- 1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Code no.4100: Bethlehem Steel Company (Shipbuilding Division) and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, 1960- 1963 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Code no.4101: DeFoe Shipbuilding Company, Bay City, Michigan and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 49, 1957-1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Code no.4102: Dravo Corporation, Engineering Works Division and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 61, 1961-1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Code no.4103: General Dynamics Electric Boat Division and Metal Trades Council of New London County, 1968-1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Code no.4104: Electric Boat Division/General Dynamics Corporation and Marine Draftsmen's Association, Port of New London, 1966- 1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Code no.4105: Ingalls Shipbuilding Corporation and Metal Trades Department, Pascagoula Metal Trades Council, 1957-1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Code no.4106: Maryland Shipbuilding and Drydock Company and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 31, 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Code no.4108: Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company and Peninsula Shipbuilders' Association, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Code no.4109: New York Shipbuilding Corporation and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Lodge 801, 1960-1966 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Code no.4114: Todd Shipyards Corporation, Los Angeles Division and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 9, 1953-1971 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Code no.4117: ALCO Products, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America Local 2054, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Code no.4119: General American Transportation Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Code no.4120: Pullman-Standard, a Division of Pullman Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Production and Maintenance Employees, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Code no.4123: United Aircraft Corporation Pratt and Whitney Aircraft Division and United Automobile Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1234, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Code no.4126: Diamond Reo Truck Division, White Motor Corporation and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 650, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Code no.4128: General Electric Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 912, 1960- 1969 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Code no.4129: National Steel and Shipbuilding Company and International Association of Bridge, Structural, and Ornamental Ironworkers Local 627, 1962-1970 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Code no.4135: Aerostructures Division, AVCO Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 735, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Code no.4138: Gibbs Shipyards, Inc. and Independent Workers Union of Florida, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Code no.4139: Chrysler Corporation, Detroit Universal Division and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 174, 1964-1970 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Code no.4140: FMC Corporation, Ordnance Division, South Charleston Plant and United Automobile Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 348, 1964-1969 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Code no.4142: Jacksonville Shipyards Inc. and Independent Workers Union of Florida, 1964-1970 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Code no.4005: Warner Gear Division, Borg Warner Corporation and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 287, 1961-1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Code no.4007: Chrysler Corporation and United Automobile Workers, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Code no.4008: Chrysler Corporation and United Automobile Workers, Office and Clerical, 1961-1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Code no.4009: Chrysler Corporation and United Automobile Workers, Parts Depots, 1958-1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Code no.4014: Dana Corporation, Axle Division and International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America, Local 903, 1961-1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Code no.4018: Eaton Yale and Towne Inc., Eaton Axle Division and Mechanics Educational Society of America, Local 21, 1968- 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Code no.4021: Fuller Transmission Division of Eaton Yale and Towne Inc. and Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 822, 1963- 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Code no.4023: General Motors Corporation and United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1968-1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Code no.4024: Kelsey-Hayes Company and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 78, 1958- 1967 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Code no.4026: King-Seeley Division, King-Seeley Corporation and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 630, CIO, 1956-1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Code no.4029: Mack Trucks Inc. and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 677, 1958- 1959 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Code no.4032: Metropolitan Body Co. and United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 505, 1959- 1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Code no.4034: Ionia Manufacturing Company and United Furniture Workers of America, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Code no.4037: Rockwell-Standard Corporation, Transmission and Axle Division Forge Division and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 174, 1959-1967 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Code no.4039: A.O. Smith Corporation, Granite City Works and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local 575, 1964-1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Code no.4041: Studebaker-Packard Corporation and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1962- 1964 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Code no.4043: Trico Products Corporation and Trico Workers Union, 1961-1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Code no.4046: Kaiser Jeep Corporation and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 12, Kaiser Jeep Unit, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Code no.4047: AVCO, Lycoming Division and International Union, Local 787, United Automobile Workers, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Code no.4051: Bendix Corporation and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1962-1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Code no.4053: Pioneer-Central Division, the Bendix Corporation and International Association of Machinists Lodge 102, 1960-1965 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Code no.4054: Bendix Aviation Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 417, 1960- 1962 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Code no.4064: Curtiss-Wright Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Aircraft Lodge 703, 1962-1966 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Code no.4069: Douglas Aircraft Co., Inc. and International Association of Machinists, Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge 720, 1962- 1968 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Code no.4072: General Dynamics Corporation, Astronautics Division and Engineers and Architects Association, San Diego Chapter, 1960- 1963 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Code no.4076: Goodyear Aerospace Corporation and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 856, 1960-1970 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Code no.4078: Jack and Heintz, Inc. and International Association of Machinists, District 54, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Code no.4085: Northrop Corporation, Ventura Division and RPA, Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Code no.4086: Piper Aircraft Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 734, 1959-1968 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Code no.5771: Western Electric Company, Inc., Distribution Organization of the Service Division and Communications Workers of America, 1967-1971 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Code no.5772: Western Electric Company, Inc., Installation Organization of the Service Division and Communications Workers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Code no.2944: West Bend Company and Allied Industrial Workers of America, Local 865, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Code no.590983: Ingersoll-Rand Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1064, District 58, 1959- 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Code no.3605: Sangamo Electric Company and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1585, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Code no.591180: Westinghouse Air Brake Company and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 610, 1961- 1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Code no.3748: Eureka Williams Company Division of National Union Electric Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1000, 1968-1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Code no.591179: Westinghouse Air Brake Company and United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, Local 610, 1969- 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Code no.4096: Pratt and Whitney Aircraft Division of United Aircraft Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1746, 1968-1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Code no.4098: American Ship Building Company and AFL-CIO affiliates, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Code no.4122: Westinghouse Air Brake Company and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America Local 610, Westinghouse Air Brake Division, 1961-1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Code no.4186: Stewart-Warner Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1031, 1962-1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Code no.4428: Bulova Watch Company, Inc. and Production Employees Group of the Bulova Watch Company, 1965-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Code no.23: Aerojet-General Corporation (Sacramento) and International Association of Machinists, Local 946, 1962-1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Code no.23: Aerojet-General Corporation (Sacramento) and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 946, 1965- 1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Code no.590924: National Homes Corp. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 2601, 1961-1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Code no.3264: TMW Division, North American Rockwell Corporation and United Steel Workers of America, Local 6996, 1969-1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Code no.4134: Norfolk Shipbuilding and Drydock Corporation and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Forgers, Blacksmiths, and Helpers of America, Local 684, 1962-1970 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Code no.591015: Aerojet-General Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 1893, District Lodge 80, 1960-1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2972: Companies of the Southern California Steel Fabricators and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local Lodge 92, 1966-1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Code no.3291: Midwest Manufacturing Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Midwest Lodge 2063, 1969-1973 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Code no.591243: Cleveland Pneumatic Tool Company and Aerol Aircraft Employees' Association, 1961-1973 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Code no.10: Martin Marietta Corporation Aerospace Group and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 766, 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2618: Ladish Co. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District 10, 1967-1973 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Code no.591170: J.H. Williams and Co. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1183, 1966-1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Code no.3272: Ingersoll-Rand Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, 1960-1972 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Code no.591210: Louis Allis Co. and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 1131, 1959-1973 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Code no.8: Hughes Aircraft Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Old Pueblo Lodge 933, 1969- 1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Code no.590931: Remington Arms Co., Inc., Bridgeport Works and Industrial Machine Office Workers Union, 1961-1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Code no.37: Pratt and Whitney Aircraft Division of United Aircraft Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Industrial Aircraft Lodge 700, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2507: Atlantic Steel Co. and United Steelworkers of America, 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Code no.570548: Textron, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1306, 1968-1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Code no.2597: Bridgeport Brass Co. and Brass Workers directly affiliated with Local 24411, 1961-1971 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Code no.2965: Grinnell Corporation and International Molders and Allied Workers, Local 376, 1961-1972 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Code no.3214: Worthington Corporation, Compressor and Engine Division and United Steelworkers of America, 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Code no.3242: Marion Power Shovel Co., Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1949, 1967-1972 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Code no.3245: Brown and Sharpe and International Association of Machinists, Lodges 1088 and 1142, District 64, 1961-1973 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Code no.3322: Danly Machine Corporation and United Mine Workers of America Local 15271, International Union of District 50, 1969- 1972 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Code no.590686: Brown and Sharpe and American Federation of Technical Engineers, Local 119, 1965-1973 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Code no.590694: Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Wright Aeronautical Division and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 300, 1961-1971 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Code no.4180: Huffman Manufacturing Co. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 5369, 1966-1972 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Series VIII: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade
  - Code no.6304: Los Angeles Markets Arbitration Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 630, 1962-1971 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Code no.6311: No Employer and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 423, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Code no.6312: Several Employers and Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity, 1961-1967 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Code no.6313: Several Employers and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Locals 975 and 977, 1960-1970 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Code no.6314: Several Employers and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 830, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Code no.6314: Several Employers and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 830, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Code no.6324: No Employer and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen of North America Local 627, Provision Salesmen and Distributors Union, 1966-1973 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Code no.6328: Illinois Association of Breweries and Illinois Beer Wholesalers Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 744, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Code no.6303: Wholesale Grocers, Chain Stores, and Retailer Owned Warehouse Operators of Minneapolis and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 544, 1964-1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Code no.290: Wholesale Bakers' Group and Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union of America, Local 31, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Code no.334: Northern New Jersey Milk Industry and Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees, Local 680, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Code no.348: California Bakery Employers Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6316: Food Employers Council, Inc. and Service and Maintenance Employees' Union, Local 399, 1959-1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Food Employers Council, Inc. and Service and Maintenance Employees' Union, Local 399, 1959-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1959 and expires on 5/31/1964. Covers an unknown number of workers in California
      Format: Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA).
    - Item 2: Food Employers Council, Inc. and Service and Maintenance Employees' Union, Local 399, 1964-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1964 and expires on 6/1/1969. Covers an unknown number of workers in California
    - Item 3: Food Employers Council, Inc. and Service and Maintenance Employees' Union, Local 399, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 11/4/1968 and expires on 10/31/1971. Covers 1000 workers in California
    - Item 4: Food Employers Council, Inc. and Service and Maintenance Employees' Union, Local 399, 1968-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 11/4/1968 and expires on 12/30/1973. Covers 600 workers in California
  - Code no.6719: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Altoona Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Amalgamated Food Employees Union, Local 590, 1959-1965 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Altoona Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Amalgamated Food Employees Union, Local 590, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 7/12/1959 and expires on 7/15/1961. Covers 1257 workers in Cumberland, MD; PA
    - Item 2: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Altoona Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Amalgamated Food Employees Union, Local 590, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 7/16/1961 and expires on 7/13/1963. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cumberland, MD; LaVale, MD; PA